RISTMI DAFFA' KHOIRI

Pontianak, West Kalimantan | <u>Portofolio</u> | <u>Github</u> | <u>Linkedin</u> | +6289526781084 | <u>devristmidaffa@gmail.com</u>

SUMMARY

Bachelor of Economics graduate with experience in marketing. A great interest in challenges and the world of technology drove me to study web development Successfully completed a full-stack web developer program at Eduwork as well as various other online courses, with a strong focus and interest in backend development. Enthusiastic to integrate business background and full-stack technical expertise, especiall backend expertise, in making a real contribution to your company.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Upload-Image (MERN)

Desember 2024

A fullstack web platform that allows users to easily manage their images. The app uses the latest technologies such as Node.js, MySQL, and React.js to provide a seamless user experience in uploading, editing, and sharing images."

Tools: Node js, React js, Postman, Bulma, Mysql

Link : Client Side | Server Side

Market-Style November 2024

Platform or application that allows sellers and buyers to carry out buying and selling transactions online. In this marketplace project, we will use React.js as a JavaScript framework to build a user interface (frontend), Fake API to provide product data that will be displayed on the platform, as well as several additional features such as login for user authentication and price sum to calculate the total price of the products purchased.

Tools: JavaScript, Reactis, Tailwind CSS, Html

Link : Github Market Style

Parkir-Web Aug 2024 - septl 2024

aims to provide a parking management system that is easily accessible via a browser. This website can be used to record, manage and monitor vehicle parking activities, both for open and closed parking areas.

Tools: HTML5, Javascript, Express.js, Node.js, Postman,

Link : Github Backend Parkir

Calculator Juli 2024

Details Creating a simple calculator using JavaScript on a web page involves using HTML for the user interface (UI), CSS for styling, and JavaScript for calculation logic. Below are the steps to create a basic calculator that can handle arithmetic operations such as addition, subtraction, multiplication, and division.

Tools: JavaScript, Html, Css
Link: <u>Github Calculator</u>
Demo: <u>Link Demo Calculator</u>

Temu Sehat Pontianak

Marketing Staff

Sep 2022 – Dec 2023

- Assist in the development and implementation of marketing strategies to increase brand awareness
 - and attract new customers.
- Plan and execute marketing campaigns both online and offline, including social media, email marketing, and promotional events.
- Conduct market research to identify trends, customer preferences, and competitor activities.
- Manage relationships with customers and business partners to ensure customer satisfaction and loyalty.

BMII ILTIZAM INDONESIA

Kubu Raya

College Program Intern - Internship

Jul 2022 – Aug 2023

- Assist in the development and implementation of marketing strategies to increase brand awareness and attract new customers.
- Plan and execute marketing campaigns both online and offline, including social media, email marketing, and promotional events.
- Conduct market research to identify trends, customer preferences, and competitor activities.
- Manage relationships with customers and business partners to ensure customer satisfaction and loyalty.

CERTIFICATION

Eduwork

Pontianak, (Online, ID)

Programmer Fullstack MERN

Mar 2023 – *Des* 2024

- At Eduwork, I took the Programmer Fullstack MERN (MongoDB, Express.js, React.js and Node.js) class.
- Students will learn the JavaScript programming language, using platforms such as Node.js (3 months) and using frameworks such as React.js (6 months) and Express.js (4 months).
- Students can organize, store and manage data in database web applications using XAMPP and MySQL relational database management system (RDBMS).
- To develop the client side (front-end), using HTML5, CSS, JavaScript (3 month) and React.js to create attractive and responsive interfaces.
- Students also learn how to manage the server side (back-end) using tools such as Github (1 month), to manage APIs using Insomnia and Postman (1 month)

MySkill

Pontianak, (Online, ID)

Working With API

September 2024

- understand how APIs work as anintermediary between clients (such as web or mobile applications) and servers.
- Learn and practice using various HTTP methods and when they are appropriate to use.
- learn how to read and understand the response body from the server, which usually contains the requested data (in JSON or XML format).
- Sertifikat Working With API.pdf

EDUCATION

University of Tanjungpura

Pontianak

Bachelor Degree – Islamic Economic

Aug 2016 – Des 2023

GPA 3.41

• Graduate of Tanjungpura University, Islamic Economics Study Program, with a deep understanding of the principles of Islamic economics and its application in the business world. Have work experience as a Marketing Staff at Temu Sehat, involved in marketing strategy development, campaign implementation, market analysis, and marketing content management. creative, proactive, and results-oriented individual, with good communication skills and able to work effectively in a team.

SKILLS, INTERESTS, & LANGUAGES

Technical Skills: HTML | CSS | Javascript | React | Github | Express | Node.js | Postman | Insomnia | MongoDB | SASS | Tailwind CSS | Axios

Soft Skills : Analysis | Teamwork | Problem Solving | Enthusiasm

Interests : Back-end Engineer | Front-end Engineer | Fullstack Engineer | Software Engineer | Electrical Engineer

Language : Bahasa indonesia (Native) | Bahasa Melayu (Proficient) | Bahasa Inggris (Beginner)